nwfcu.org 2011-12-10

# 

                                                                                                                    Rev. 12/11
                     WHAT DOES NORTHWEST FEDERAL CREDIT UNION
FACTS                DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                 Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                     consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
                     we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                     understand what we do.
What?                The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                     have with us. This information can include:
                     ■ Social Security number and income
                     ■ Account balances and payment history
                     ■ Credit history and credit scores
                     When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in
                     this notice.
How?                 All financial companies need to share their members’ personal information to run their everyday
                     business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’
                     personal information; the reasons Northwest Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether
                     you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information                   Does NWFCU share?           Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes –
such as to process your transactions, maintain
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal                         Yes                             No
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes –
to offer our products and services to you                                  Yes                             No
For joint marketing with other financial companies                         No                       We don’t share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
information about your transactions and experiences                        No                       We don’t share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
information about your creditworthiness                                    No                       We don’t share
For our affiliates to market to you                                        No                       We don’t share
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                         No                       We don’t share
Questions?           Call 703-709-8901 (1-866-709-8901 toll-free) or go to www.nwfcu.org

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?  Northwest Federal Credit Union
What we do
How does NWFCU protect my      To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
personal information?          and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                               These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                               and buildings.
How does NWFCU collect my      We collect your personal information, for example, when you
personal information?          ■  open an account or deposit money
                               ■  pay your bills or apply for a loan
                               ■ use your credit or debit card
                               We also collect your personal information from others, such as
                               credit bureaus, affiliates or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                               ■  sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information
                                  about your creditworthiness
                               ■ affiliates from using your information to market to you
                               ■ sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                               State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                               limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                     Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                               financial and nonfinancial companies.
                               ■  Northwest Federal Credit Union does not share with its affiliate,
                                  Northwest Financial, LLC.
Nonaffiliates                  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                               financial and nonfinancial companies.
                               ■  Northwest Federal Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates so
                                  they can market to you.
Joint marketing                A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                               together market financial products or services to you.
                               ■  Northwest Federal Credit Union does not jointly market.
                                                                                               PSB (12/2011) 8M
